One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Beyond the heavy rain is a rainbow
hageshii ame no mukou kakaru niji wo mita
I'll know the easy answer's a lie
tayasui kotae wa uso dato shiru darou
Vow not to back down to the shouting
dekai koe nanka ni makenai to chikatte
I need you alone to understand tomorrow
anata hitori ni wakatte hoshii ashita
You gave me the time of my life
yume no youna jikan kureta anata
What do I look like? An ANGEL or a DEVIL...
watashi wa dou mieteruno? sorega tenshi ka akuma ka
Beyond the dawn, beyond the dawn
yoake no mukou yoake no mukou
There's so much I want to tell you
hanashitai koto takusan arun da
Filled with love, with love
ai kometa ai kometa
That can't be written down in a letter
tegami ni kakikirenai omoi da
A small hand in search of eternity
eien wo sagashita chiisana tenohira
"A Fleeting Moment of Happiness -
Kumachi and Ginny"
Sorbet Kingdom,
South Blue
Going back 30 years ago.
This is the Sorbet Kingdom
in the South Blue.
Eight years after the God Valley Incident.
Heave ho...
Help me, Kumachi.
You got it.
I feel much better.
Thank you.
Who's next?
Me.
My back hurts and I can't sleep well.
Help me again.
You've always been a great help, Kumachi.
I've been attending this church
since your father's time.
So I was surprised
when all of you suddenly disappeared...
We were relieved when you came back.
I'm sure your parents are happy somewhere,
knowing that their son
has become a great pastor.
Bartholomew Kuma
(Age 17), Pastor
The pain is gone!
Thank you so much.
What a blessing.
He'll remove any kind of pain...
They're indeed Miracle Hands.
Hey, Kumachi.
Can't you do this on weekdays, too?
No! Just Sundays!
You don't even pay for this.
You're so shameless, you old codgers!
Here comes the mean Ginny!
Oh, shut up!
This is not a campground or a hospital!
Go away!
She has such a foul mouth,
but since she's so pretty...
Ginny (Age 21)
Men from the town
never stop asking her out!
Don't change the subject!
Well, she's already got Kumachi.
What?
Oh, I think we nailed it.
You can't deceive us.
We're not living longer for nothing.
That's enough!
If you're done here, go home already!
Don't be so mean, Ginny.
Seeing Kumachi's face helps us relax.
Glad to hear that.
You're being too sweet to them!
I'd pay Kumachi as much as I could...
But it's already hard enough to get by
because of the Heavenly Tribute...
And now we've got this new king.
King Bekori is famously
cold and heartless.
If we fall ill,
we can't pay the Heavenly Tribute...
And then he'll lock us up!
How terrible.
I heard that an old man who was jailed
the other day starved to death.
Starved!
The king won't even feed prisoners.
What a skinflint.
But he sucks up to the Celestial Dragons.
He's really despicable.
Old people who are poor can't survive.
We have to be healthy, or we'll die.
If it's a minor ailment or pain,
I can take it away for you.
Come every week.
- Are you sure?
- We appreciate it, Kumachi.
This is all we can give you...
Eat it with Ginny later.
Thank you!
Goodbye!
Please help us again!
Yeah, see you next week!
How can you do this to yourself
every week?
They don't even know
that you're suffering.
There's no other choice...
The mass of pain and suffering...
...won't just disappear
until someone accepts it.
If left untouched,
it'd return to the person it came from.
Most importantly, I feel delighted...
...to see everyone happy.
I'm sorry for worrying you.
I'll train harder and become stronger...
That's not the issue.
I'm okay now.
You sure?
They gave us some food, right?
Let's eat.
Yay! Mealtime!
Let's eat!
Let's eat.
Yummy!
Hey, Ginny.
If it's sunny tomorrow,
can we go somewhere?
Sounds good! How about a barbecue?
It's right around the time
for the salmon run,
so maybe by the river?
Yeah. Let's do that.
Ya-hoo! Can't wait!
25 Years Ago
Time rolled on, but when Kuma was 22...
Thank you as always.
Good morning, Kumachi.
Good morning, Ginny.
Do you want me to make some coffee?
Yeah.
I love the coffee you make!
It'll be ready soon.
I've got an idea!
Let's get married, Kumachi!
What?!
No!
Why?! Let's just get married!
I know you really love me!
I promise I'll make you happy!
I know I'll be happy, but...
I'm the only one who has Buccaneer blood!
My wife doesn't!
Let her and my boy go!
Your mother's dead...
Please understand, Ginny.
I don't want to bring you misery.
Kumachi!
L-Look!
Another article about the Freedom Fighters.
They've incited protests
in various countries
and have been placed on the wanted list!
Dragon. He's so cool.
I'm sure he's thought of as a hero.
I want to go out to the sea someday
and devote my life...
...to saving others, too.
Just like Nika, the Warrior of Liberation.
Hey! Are you here?!
Who is it?
It's still early in the morning.
Hi, Kuma!
Sorry to bother you this early.
What's up?
It's the lovely Ginny!
We caught a huge haul today.
Please take some fish!
Oh! Thanks, Gyogyo!
Ouch!
She's mad at you.
Dummy.
And then 22 years ago,
a major incident took place
in the Sorbet Kingdom.
Royal City,
Sorbet Kingdom
Wait!
Kuma
(Age 25)
What are you doing?!
Release those you kidnapped!
Who is this big loser?
He's a pastor from the South.
You're just a pastor, stay out of this!
Are you trying to defy the Royal Army?!
Kumachi, help!
Don't move, old bag!
Hey, Father!
I'm sure you heard
that the laws have changed.
Now we're free to use people from the South
however we want.
You're turning them into slaves?!
Stop it right now!
K-Kumachi!
It's His Majesty's policy.
We'll drive them to work hard.
Until they die.
Stop!
Damn you!
You crossed the line!
You rebels!
Enslaving you isn't enough!
I'm gonna kill you!
What's that?!
It's an unforgivable sin!
Your Majesty.
This policy is not well received
among the people of the kingdom.
Won't the people resist?
Don't worry.
People tend to be easily swayed by labels.
Soon, they'll start looking down on the South.
Right...
Starting today, only the north part of the island is the Sorbet Kingdom.
The amount of the Heavenly Tribute
to be paid to the Government...
...is determined
by the number of citizens.
Thus, the South, with its many old people
who can't pay much Heavenly Tribute,
Kuma's Church
Sorbet Kingdom
Elderly Village
Lawless Area
Castle and Royal City
is dragging us down.
If we cut them off,
this kingdom will become rich.
Kuma's Church
Elderly Village
Lawless Area
It's that easy...
Prison
Why are you guys in here, too?
We ran amok,
saying we wanted you back...
They beat the hell out of us.
We did something out of character...
But it felt good.
This is wrong...
Just because you're living in the South,
you'll be enslaved...
Kumachi...
Ginny. This country is turning into a place
where the poor suffer harsh discrimination.
King Bekori is the Celestial Dragons' puppet.
This policy was put in his head from above.
If we want to rebel against this country,
we must be determined
to fight the World Government.
Who are you people?!
Your Majesty! Please evacuate!
I won't let you escape.
You stupid Celestial Dragon wannabe!
How sickening!
D-Don't tell me you're...
Thanks to outside intervention,
the Sorbet Kingdom narrowly avoided
that evil policy.
The king has given in!
The slave policy is repealed!
Thank goodness!
I don't wanna live in such a country.
Seems like your favorite guy
really created a scene.
I'm sure you'll like him at first sight,
Dragon.
Kuma! Ginny! You guys were caught!
I'm here to get you out!
What?! Iva-chan?!
Big Bro?!
And that man you're with...
Dragon?!
Hey, Kuma!
If you're still the same man
you were then,
join us to change the world together!
Okay!
I'm going, too!
Heehaw!
The Freedom Fighters, who transformed
people's anger at governments into protests,
decided to take up arms...
...in response to the advent of the Pirate Era
and the tragedy of Ohara.
Adding Kuma to their twin pillars of
Dragon and Ivankov,
they transformed themselves
into the Revolutionary Army,
which would become infamous
throughout the world.
We still don't have enough money.
Like mercenaries, we'll help those
who aspire to rebel to overthrow their kings.
Those who wish to join will be taught
how to use weapons and fight with them.
Eventually, I want it to be a huge army
spread across the world.
When did you learn how to
use weapons, Dragon?
I spent a short time in the Marines.
Unfortunately,
I couldn't find any "justice" there.
Both the Marines
and the Revolutionary Army...
...just want to help people.
I'm with you to the end, Dragon.
Me too!
You won't regret it.
Oh! You returned, Kumachi!
I was worried about you all.
I'll be back to see you from time to time.
How sweet.
Is anybody sick or hurt?
And eight more years passed.
14 years ago, in a certain kingdom...
Revolutionary Army Captain,
Eastern Forces, Ginny
Kumachi! Kumachi!
You look happy, Ginny-san.
Oh, is it showing?
Because tomorrow...
...we'll meet up with Kumachi's group.
I really can't wait!
I wish I were Captain Kuma.
He's loved by everyone's crush.
What? You've got a crush on me?!
Ew! You snotty brats!
So harsh.
Baltigo, Revolutionary
Army Headquarters
Dragon-san! Dragon-san!
Ginny's been...
...abducted?!
I'm sorry!
The enemy caught us off guard...
I can't protect anyone again
mata daremo mamorenai no
It's my fault that the voice is fading away
kiekakaru koe wa boku no sei
I don't even have time to look down
utsumuku hima mo nai no
Gravel marks on my palms
tenohira ni tsuku jari no ato
Start moving again, my ship
mata ugokidase boku no fune yo
Though I can't fly in the broad sky
hiroi sora wa tobenai kedo
I can light up the deep sea
fukai umi wa teraseru kara
We
bokura wa
EVERYDAY owarenai
EVERYDAY, can't let this be the end
EVERYDAY makerenai
EVERYDAY, can't be defeated
We have something here to protect
mamoru mono ga koko niwa aru
This may not be what I expected
yosou chigai kamo?
But we can't stop now
tomarenai yo mou
We go on, sharing loneliness
kodoku wo ima wakeai susumu
Don't be afraid
ojikedzukuna yo
I'm not the same person I was that day
ano hi no boku to chigau kara
No one can stand in my way
dare nimo jama dekinai yo
Now, move aside
saa doite
Conquer the world, believe in the future
sekai wo seishite mirai wo shinjite
Count up the nights
ikutsu mono yoru kazoete
What did you see? What did you learn?
nani wo mite nani wo shitte
To realize what was important
taisetsu na koto ni kidzuita no